Bess Lomax Hawes collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Guides to the Collections in the Archive of Folk Culture
Bess Lomax Hawes collection circa 1890s-2009
AFC 2014/008
Bess Lomax Hawes, 1921-2009
13,480 items
45 containers
394 folders in 31 boxes
33 sound tape reels: analog; various sizes.
68 sound cassettes: analog.
1 sound disc (CD-R): digital; 4 3/4 in.
circa 2,000 photographic prints: black and white, color; various sizes.
circa 500 photographs: film negatives.
circa 200 drawings.
8 videocassettes (VHS): color, sound; 1/2 in.
2 video discs (DVD): digital; 4 3/4 in.
approximately 20 items; various sizes.
Archive of Folk Culture, American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Papers and audiovisual materials relating to the career and personal life of folk arts administrator, folklorist, filmmaker, musician, and teacher Bess Lomax Hawes, most from 1960-2001. Includes work produced by Hawes in her work as a professor at San Fernando Valley State College in Northridge, California, and as head of the National Endowment for the Arts Folk Arts Program in Washington, DC. The collection includes writings, correspondence, business records, musical transcriptions and photographs. Also includes artwork produced by her husband, Baldwin "Butch" Hawes.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Bergey, Barry--Correspondence.; Bulger, Peggy A.--Correspondence.; Cohen, Ronald D., 1940-; Dane, Barbara.; Duggan, Shirley Lomax, 1905-1996--Correspondence.; Dundes, Alan--Correspondence.; Elder, J. D. (Jacob Delworth), 1913-2003--Correspondence.; Hanks, Nancy, 1927-1983--Correspondence.; Hawes, Bess Lomax, 1921-2009; Hawes, Bess Lomax, 1921-2009--Correspondence.; Hawes, Bess Lomax, 1921-2009--Ethnomusicological collections.; Hawes, Butch, 1919-1971; Hawes, Butch, 1919-1971--Correspondence.; Hodsoll, Francis Samuel Monaise--Correspondence.; Jabbour, Alan--Correspondence.; Jones, Bessie, 1902-1984--Correspondence--Interviews.; Leadbelly, 1885-1949.; Lomax, Alan, 1915-2002--Correspondence.; Lomax, Bess Brown, 1880-1931--Correspondence.; Lomax, John A. (John Avery), 1867-1948--Correspondence.; Lomax, John A., Jr. (John Avery), 1907-1974--Correspondence.; Lomax, Ruby T. (Ruby Terrill)--Correspondence.; McCann, Gordon, 1931- --Correspondence.; Rinzler, Ralph--Correspondence.; Seeger, Pete, 1919-2014--Correspondence.; Seeger, Toshi--Correspondence.; Willett, E. Henry, 1951- --Correspondence.
Organizations
Almanac Singers.; American Folklife Center.; American Folklore Society.; Association for Cultural Equity.; California Folklore Society.; California State University, Northridge.; Festival of American Folklife.; Festival of Pacific Arts (6th: 1992: Rarotonga, Cook Islands); National Endowment for the Arts. Folk Arts Program.; National Endowment for the Arts. Folk Arts Program.; National Endowment for the Arts. National Heritage Fellowship.; Sea Island Singers.
Subjects
African Americans--Music.; Arts administrators--United States--Biography.; Children's songs.; Ethnic arts.; Ethnomusicology.; Folk art.; Folk dancing--United States.; Folk festivals.; Folk music--United States.; Folk songs, English.; Folklore--California.; Folklore--Study and teaching.; Folklore--United States--Congresses.; Folklorists' writings, American.; Folklorists--United States--Correspondence.; Indians of North America--California--Music.; Music--Bermuda Islands.; Music--Cook Islands.; Music--Guam.; Music--Hawaii.; Music--Micronesia (Federated States); Music--Northern Mariana Islands.; Music--Samoa.; Music--Trinidad and Tobago.; Music--United States.; Music--West Indies.; Public folklore--Washington (D.C.); Shape-note singing.; Singing games--Antilles, Lesser.; Singing games--Sea Islands.; Women folklorists--United States.
Form/Genre
Clippings.; Correspondence.; Diaries.; Documentary films.; Drawings.; Field notes.; Interviews.; Manuscripts.; Oral histories.; Photograph albums.; Photographs.; Scores.; Scrapbooks.; Songbooks.; Sound recordings.; Speeches.; Videocassettes.
Arrangement
The collection is divided into the following series: I. Manuscripts; II. Sound recordings; III. Graphic materials; IV. Moving images; V. Artifacts.
Acquisition
Donated by Naomi Bishop, Corey Denos and Nicholas Hawes in 2014.
Accruals
No further accruals are expected.
Related Material
Bess Lomax Hawes Student Folklore Collection, 1958-1977 at the California State University, Northridge
Access and Restrictions
The collection is open for research use. Access restrictions apply. Please contact the Folklife Reading Room before requesting materials: http://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Online Content
Part of the Bess Lomax Hawes Collection is available on the Library of Congress Web site at https://www.loc.gov/collections/bess-lomax-hawes/about-this-collection/
Biographical Note
Bess Lomax Hawes (1921-2009) was a folklorist, teacher, musician, writer, filmmaker, and folk arts administrator. Named for her mother, Bess Brown Lomax, Jr. was exposed at a young age to folk music performance and fieldwork through her father, John A. Lomax, and brother, Alan Lomax. As a teenager she transcribed music from field recording sessions, and provided assistance to her father, brother Alan, and composer Ruth Crawford Seeger during their work on Our Singing Country (1941), a collection of American folk songs and ballads. After graduating from Bryn Mawr College in 1941, she moved to New York City, where she performed with the Almanac Singers, including Pete Seeger, Woody Guthrie, her future husband, artist Butch Hawes, and others. She moved with her husband to Cambridge, Massachusetts, where she taught guitar lessons, wrote music and cared for her young children.
In 1952, Hawes moved with her family to California, where she taught guitar and courses in folklore and anthropology at San Fernando Valley State College (now California State University, Northridge). As professor, she wrote a number of academic papers and was an active participant in the California Folklore Society, which she served as president from 1971-1973. While on the faculty at San Fernando Valley State, Hawes completed her M.A. in Folklore from the University of California, Berkeley, studying under folklorist Alan Dundes. She made four films while working in California: Georgia Sea Island Singers (1964), Buckdancer (1965), Pizza Pizza Daddy-O (1967) and Say Old Man, Can You Play the Fiddle (1970).
In 1977, Hawes moved to Washington, D.C. to serve as head of the Folk Arts Program at the National Endowment for the Arts, and stayed on for a fifteen-year tenure. At NEA she raised the public profile of the folk arts, establishing apprenticeship and other grant programs to support folk artists with skills as varied as music and dance, basketmaking, and pottery. A crowning achievement at the NEA was the establishment of the National Heritage Fellowship program to honor folk artists for lifetime achievement and contributions to traditional arts in the United States. Hawes traveled widely for her work at NEA, both nationally and internationally. She wrote several books: Step It Down (1972), co-authored with Bessie Jones; Brown Girl in the Ring (1997), co-authored with Alan Lomax and J.D. Elder; and Sing It Pretty (2008), a memoir. In 1993 Hawes received the National Medal of Arts from president Bill Clinton.
Scope and Content
Collection of manuscripts, sound recordings, graphic materials, moving images and artifacts representing the life work of folk arts administrator, folklorist, filmmaker, musician, and teacher Bess Lomax Hawes. The bulk of the collection materials date from 1960 through 2000 and document Hawes’s work as a professor in the anthropology department at San Fernando Valley State College, as a coordinator for the Smithsonian Institution’s Festival of American Folklife, and as the first head of the National Endowment for the Arts Folk Arts Program. The collection also includes documentation of Hawes’s family life and work as a musician and teacher.
Formats include correspondence, writings and speeches, musical transcriptions, school records, memos, business records, reports, teaching materials, travel documentation, field and research notes, clippings, awards, sound recordings, moving images, photographs, and artwork.
Container List
- Series I: Manuscripts, Note: Some of Hawes’s San Fernando Valley State College (SFVSC) students’ papers are included in the series, though most are in the Bess Lomax Hawes Student Folklore Collection at the California State University, Northridge (formerly SFVSC).
  - Finding aid, 2016 (Box-folder 01.01a)
  - California Festival (1975), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 01.01)
  - Pacific Islands, Festival of American Folklife, 1975 (Box-folder 01.02)
  - Native Americans, Festival of American Folklife, 1976 (Box-folder 01.03)
  - Hispanic Week, Festival of American Folklife, 1976 (Box-folder 01.04)
  - Regional, Festival of American Folklife, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 01.05)
  - Festival of American Folklife Evaluations, 1976 (Box-folder 01.06)
  - Children's Area, Festival of American Folklife, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 01.07)
  - Names/addresses, Festival of American Folklife, 1976 (Box-folder 01.08)
  - Chronological file, Festival of American Folklife, 1975 (Box-folder 01.09)
  - Chronological file, Festival of American Folklife, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 01.10)
  - Press releases, Festival of American Folklife, 1975 (Box-folder 01.11)
  - Trip reports, Nancy Hanks, 1977, Hanks was director of the NEA at the time. (Box-folder 01.12)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1975, Mostly concerning American Folklore Society and Festival of American Folklife business. (Box-folder 01.13)
  - Southern California Academy of Sciences, 1971, Correspondence mostly concerning annual meeting. (Box-folder 01.14)
  - Society for Ethnomusicology, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 01.15)
  - Regional festivals and meetings, 1963-1971 (Box-folder 01.16)
  - Topanga Banjo and Fiddle Contest, 1962-1973, Bess Lomax Hawes helped organize this event. (Box-folder 02.01)
  - Regional folklore societies, miscellaneous, 1961-1975 (Box-folder 02.02)
  - Smithsonian research publications, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 02.03)
  - Festival of American Folklife, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 02.04)
  - Smithsonian, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 02.05)
  - Festival of American Folklife, regional recipes, circa 1975 (Box-folder 02.06)
  - Society for the Survey of North American Culture, Festival of American Folklife, 1976 (Box-folder 02.07)
  - Family folklore, Festival of American Folklife, 1976 (Box-folder 02.08)
  - Bess's personnel papers, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 02.09)
  - Correspondence, Smithsonian Festival of American Folklife, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 02.10)
  - Henry Willett, 1977-1989 (Box-folder 03.01)
  - Indian holdings, Library of Congress, 1978-1985, Mostly about Federal Cylinder Project. (Box-folder 03.02)
  - Tennessee Tombigbee Project, Library of Congress, 1978-1985 (Box-folder 03.03)
  - In-house memos, NEA, 1978-1993 (Box-folder 03.04)
  - NEA Folk Arts program reports, 1979-1995, Includes annual reports and information about folk arts programming history, NEA fellows and interview with BLH. (Box-folder 03.05)
  - Commentary of the Folk Arts program, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 03.06)
  - Staff/panel commentary, NEA, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 03.07)
  - Folk arts public commentary, 1978-1992 (Box-folder 03.08)
  - Folk Arts grants, 1980-1993 (Box-folder 03.09)
  - Conference: Sustainable Folk Arts Programming, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 03.10)
  - Tours: ethnic and overseas, 1979-1987 (Box-folder 03.11)
  - Alabama trip field notes, 1992 (Box-folder 03.12)
  - Site visit reports, 1982-1991 (Box-folder 04.01)
  - Correspondence, January-June, 1977 (Box-folder 04.02)
  - Correspondence, July-December, 1977 (Box-folder 04.03)
  - Correspondence, January-June, 1978 (Box-folder 04.04)
  - Correspondence, July-December, 1978 (Box-folder 04.05)
  - Correspondence, January-June, 1979 (Box-folder 04.06)
  - Correspondence, July-December, 1979 (Box-folder 04.07)
  - Correspondence, January-June, 1980 (Box-folder 04.08)
  - Correspondence, July-December, 1980 (Box-folder 04.09)
  - Correspondence, January-June, 1981 (Box-folder 04.10)
  - Correspondence, July-December, 1981 (Box-folder 04.11)
  - Correspondence, January-June, 1982 (Box-folder 05.01)
  - Correspondence, July-December, 1982 (Box-folder 05.02)
  - Correspondence, January-June, 1983 (Box-folder 05.03)
  - Correspondence, July-December, 1983 (Box-folder 05.04)
  - Correspondence, January-June, 1984 (Box-folder 05.05)
  - Correspondence, July-December, 1984 (Box-folder 05.06)
  - Folklife legislation and legal considerations, 1982 (Box-folder 05.07)
  - Feasibility study for touring folk arts, 1985 (Box-folder 05.08)
  - Folk Arts statistics, 1979-1994 (Box-folder 05.09)
  - NEA-period correspondence, 1980-1987, Includes professional and personal correspondence. (Box-folder 05.10)
  - Policy letters, 1979-1987 (Box-folder 05.11)
  - State Folk Arts Coordinator reports, 1981-1993 (Box-folder 05.12)
  - Apprenticeship program, 1983-2001 (Box-folder 05.13)
  - Barry Bergey speeches and publications, 1994 (Box-folder 06.01)
  - David Lowenthal publications, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 06.02)
  - Wenner-Gren Conference, 1981 (Box-folder 06.03)
  - Woody Guthrie information, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 06.04)
  - California Folklore Society, 1966-1974 (Box-folder 06.05)
  - California Folklore Society meeting (1967), 1967 (Box-folder 06.06)
  - California Folklore Society meeting (1969), 1968-1969 (Box-folder 06.07)
  - California Folklore Society meeting (1970), 1970 (Box-folder 06.08)
  - California Folklore Society meeting (1971), 1970-1971, Bess Lomax Hawes was president of California Folklore Society from 1971-1973. (Box-folder 06.09)
  - California Folklore Society meeting (1972), 1971-1972, Includes copy of CFS constitution; Bess Lomax Hawes was president of California Folklore Society from 1971-1973. (Box-folder 06.10)
  - California Folklore Society meeting (1973), 1972-1974, Bess Lomax Hawes was president of California Folklore Society from 1971-1973. (Box-folder 07.01)
  - California Folklore Society meeting (1974), 1974 (Box-folder 07.02)
  - California Folklore Society meeting (1975), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 07.03)
  - National Folk Dance, 1984 (Box-folder 07.04)
  - Tap and square dance, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 07.05)
  - Ronald D. Cohen correspondence and papers, 1993 (Box-folder 07.06)
  - Western Folklore, 1967-1973, Regarding editorial and other administrative matters. (Box-folder 07.07)
  - Vita, 1975-2004 (Box-folder 07.08)
  - Vita, 1976-1998 (Box-folder 07.09)
  - Retirement tributes (NEA), 1992 (Box-folder 07.10)
  - Business records (1992), 1992 (Box-folder 07.11)
  - Business records (1993), 1992-1993 (Box-folder 07.12)
  - Business records (1993), 1993 (Box-folder 07.13)
  - Correspondence (1993), 1991-1993, Photograph of man laying sampietrini attached to note from Pete Seeger. (Box-folder 07.14)
  - Correspondence (1994), 1993-1994 (Box-folder 07.15)
  - Business records (1994), 1994 (Box-folder 07.16)
  - Business records (1994), 1994-1995 (Box-folder 08.01)
  - Business records (1995), 1994-1995 (Box-folder 08.02)
  - Correspondence (1995), 1995 (Box-folder 08.03)
  - Correspondence (1996), 1995-1996 (Box-folder 08.04)
  - Consults (1995), 1994-1995 (Box-folder 08.05)
  - Business records (1996), 1995-1996 (Box-folder 08.06)
  - Business records(1996), 1995-1997 (Box-folder 08.07)
  - Business records (1997), 1997-1998 (Box-folder 08.08)
  - Consults/correspondence (1997), 1996-1997 (Box-folder 08.09)
  - Business records (1998), 1998-1999 (Box-folder 08.10)
  - Consults/correspondence (1998), 1998-1999 (Box-folder 08.11)
  - Business records (1999), 1999 (Box-folder 08.12)
  - Business records (2000), 2000 (Box-folder 09.01)
  - Business records (2001), 2001 (Box-folder 09.02)
  - Correspondence (2001), 2001 (Box-folder 09.03)
  - Business records (2002), 2002 (Box-folder 09.04)
  - Correspondence (2002), 2002 (Box-folder 09.05)
  - Business records (2004), 2004 (Box-folder 09.06)
  - Business records (2006-2008), 2006-2008 (Box-folder 09.07)
  - Dr. Bill Peck, 1983-1994 (Box-folder 09.08)
  - Article about MTA song, 2008, Published in Dissent, Spring 2008. (Box-folder 09.09)
  - American Folklore Society, 1970-1991, Includes correspondence of Citizens Committee for an American Folklife Center, and BLH "Fellow of the American Folklore Society" certificate. (Box-folder 09.10)
  - American Folklore Society Fellows, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 09.11)
  - Association for Cultural Equity, 1984-1997 (Box-folder 09.12)
  - Association for Cultural Equity, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 09.13)
  - Cowboy stuff, circa 1976-1996 (Box-folder 09.14)
  - Grantmakers in the Arts Conference, 1995 (Box-folder 09.15)
  - Lead Belly, 1965-1995 (Box-folder 09.16)
  - Library of Congress, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 09.17)
  - California State University, Northridge, Emeritus, 1995-1998, California State University, Northridge (CSUN) is the current name of the former San Fernando Valley State College (Box-folder 09.18)
  - Brown Girl in the Ring, 1995-2001, Correspondence with J.D. Elder (Box-folder 09.19)
  - National Heritage Award Winners, circa 1996 (Box-folder 10.01)
  - Oregon Historical Society: folklife program, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 10.02)
  - Appreciation, 1978-1995 (Box-folder 10.03)
  - Native American cultural retention, 1977 (Box-folder 10.04)
  - National Heritage Fellowship documentation, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 10.05)
  - National Heritage Fellowship documentation, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 10.06)
  - National Heritage Fellowship documentation, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 10.07)
  - National Heritage Fellowship documentation, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 10.08)
  - National Heritage Fellowship documentation, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 10.09)
  - NEA Bess Lomax Hawes Award, 2000 (Box-folder 10.10)
  - National Medal of Arts, 1993 (Box-folder 10.11)
  - National Heritage Fellowship programs, 1983-1991 (Box-folder 10.12)
  - National Heritage Fellowship programs, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 10.13)
  - NEA retirement letters, 1992, Includes letters from a number of prominent individuals, including President George H. W. Bush, Pete and Toshi Seeger, and Studs Terkel (Box-folder 10.14)
  - Travel, general, 1982-1995 (Box-folder 11.01)
  - Australia, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 11.02)
  - Australia/South Pacific, 1981-1994 (Box-folder 11.03)
  - Micronesia, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 11.04)
  - Micronesia, 1987-1995, Includes type-written notes by Alan Lomax (Box-folder 11.05)
  - Bess's journal, Micronesia, 1980 (Box-folder 11.06)
  - Friends of Micronesia, 1973-1974, Fall 1971 and Winter 1974 (Box-folder 11.07)
  - Guam, 1982-1995 (Box-folder 11.08)
  - Hawaii, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 11.09)
  - Hawaii, 1984-1994 (Box-folder 12.01)
  - Hawaii, 1988-2000 (Box-folder 12.02)
  - Hawaii visit correspondence, 1987 (Box-folder 12.03)
  - Bess's journal, Russia (U.S.S.R.), 1974 (Box-folder 12.04)
  - Travel--Caribbean, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 12.05)
  - Bermuda, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 12.06)
  - North Carolina Pottery, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 12.07)
  - Northern Marianas, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 12.08)
  - Northern Marianas, 1983-1994 (Box-folder 12.09)
  - Pacific Festival, Cooks, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 12.10)
  - Pacific Festival, Cooks, 1992 (Box-folder 12.11)
  - Pacific Festival, Cooks, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 13.01)
  - Pacific islands travel diary, 1987 (Box-folder 13.02)
  - Northern Ireland, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 13.03)
  - Samoa, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 13.04)
  - Samoa, 1987-1992, Map of Samoa removed to oversize box. (Box-folder 13.05)
  - Samoa, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 13.06)
  - Taiwan, 1993 (Box-folder 13.07)
  - Trinidad/Tobago, circa 1996 (Box-folder 13.08)
  - Bess's teaching song sheets (1 of 5), circa 1960-1975 (Box-folder 14.01)
  - Bess's teaching song sheets (2 of 5), circa 1960-1975 (Box-folder 14.02)
  - Bess's teaching song sheets (3 of 5), circa 1960-1975 (Box-folder 14.03)
  - Bess's teaching song sheets (4 of 5), circa 1960-1975 (Box-folder 14.04)
  - Bess's teaching song sheets (5 of 5), circa 1960-1975 (Box-folder 14.05)
  - Oh Mary and the Baby song sheets, 1960-1975 (Box-folder 14.06)
  - "Northfield" song sheets, circa 1960-1975 (Box-folder 14.07)
  - "The Promised Land"/"Gift to be Simple" song sheets, 1960-1975 (Box-folder 14.08)
  - New song sheets, circa 1960-1975 (Box-folder 14.09)
  - Woody Guthrie song sheets, circa 1960-1975 (Box-folder 14.10)
  - Ballads song sheets, circa 1960-1975 (Box-folder 14.11)
  - "Saints' Delight" song sheet, circa 1960-1975 (Box-folder 14.12)
  - "Wondrous Love" song sheets, circa 1960-1975 (Box-folder 14.13)
  - "Windham" L. M. song sheets, circa 1960-1975 (Box-folder 14.14)
  - F minor shape note scale song sheets, circa 1960-1975 (Box-folder 14.15)
  - Guitar teaching outlines and materials, 1958-1962, Includes syllabi and other materials for guitar classes Bess Lomax Hawes taught at UCLA (Box-folder 14.16)
  - San Fernando Valley State College syllabi, lectures, exams, 1956-1973 (Box-folder 15.01)
  - Joan Rayfield correspondence, 1972-1973, Correspondence from Ivory Coast and Canada (Box-folder 15.02)
  - American Folk Music, teaching course outline, 1968, Fall course (Box-folder 15.03)
  - Teaching, 1973, Lecture notes for Ethnological Music course (Box-folder 15.04)
  - San Fernando Valley State College student support letters, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 15.05)
  - Brag sheet -- extracurricular activities (1 of 2), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 15.06)
  - Brag sheet -- extracurricular activities (2 of 2), circa 1965-1975 (Box-folder 15.07)
  - San Fernando Valley State College faculty support letters, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 15.08)
  - Graduate work and teaching, 1966-1970, Includes information about University of Colorado Summer Institute in Anthropology; includes graduate school application information (Box-folder 15.09)
  - Personnel papers, Bess, 1958-1974 (Box-folder 16.01)
  - UC Berkeley/UCLA, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 16.02)
  - UC Berkeley/UCLA, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 16.03)
  - UCLA Folk Belief Project, 1963-1975 (Box-folder 16.04)
  - University of Colorado seminar (1 of 2), 1967 (Box-folder 16.05)
  - University of Colorado seminar (2 of 2), 1967 (Box-folder 16.06)
  - Correspondence with students, 1964-1979 (Box-folder 16.07)
  - Student evaluations, circa 1970, circa 1970, Course evaluations (Box-folder 17.01)
  - Interesting responses to exam questions, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 17.02)
  - SFVSC -- student papers, organized alphabetically by song: A, circa 1970 (Box-folder 17.03)
  - SFVSC -- student papers, organized alphabetically by song: B, circa 1963-1968 (Box-folder 17.04)
  - SFVSC -- student papers, organized alphabetically by song: C, circa 1963-1971 (Box-folder 17.05)
  - SFVSC – student papers, organized alphabetically by song: D, 1963-1973 (Box-folder 17.06)
  - SFVSC – student papers, organized alphabetically by song: E, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 17.07)
  - SFVSC – student papers, organized alphabetically by song: F (1 of 2), 1962-1967 (Box-folder 17.08)
  - SFVSC – student papers, organized alphabetically by song: F (2 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 17.09)
  - SFVSC – student papers, organized alphabetically by song: G, 1971 (Box-folder 18.01)
  - SFVSC – student papers, organized alphabetically by song: H, 1972 (Box-folder 18.02)
  - SFVSC – student papers, organized alphabetically by song: J, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 18.03)
  - SFVSC – student papers, organized alphabetically by song: L, 1962 (Box-folder 18.04)
  - SFVSC – student papers, organized alphabetically by song: M, circa 1970 (Box-folder 18.05)
  - SFVSC – student papers, organized alphabetically by song: O, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 18.06)